这是什么
Hello!
What's this?
对了是那个女生的电话
Oh, right! it's that girl's phone number.
在这里一个很辣的女生
There it is. just a phone number...
给我的电话
...a really hot girl gave me.
也没什么
It's no big deal. i mean, it is
只是她家的电话
her home phone st of birthdays
真是的差点就把这个宝贝掉了
Almost lost this baby!
可爱的亚曼达把电话给我  我却掉了
The lovely amanda gives me her number, and i go and drop it.
谢谢
Thank you.
-你的生日是几号  -5月5号  怎么了
-when's your birthday? -may 5th. why?
我只是在记大家的生日
I'm making a list of birthdays.
-我是12月  -随便
-mine's december -yeah, whatever.
她真漂亮
She's pretty!
好漂亮  真好  真漂亮
Pretty, pretty girl. the pretty she's pretty.
去约她嘛
Go ask her out.
-有什么大不了的  -我搞不好会死
-what's the worst that could happen? -i could die.
一个人的确很难熬
Yeah, it's tough being single.
所以我很高兴我认识了亚曼达
That's why i'm so glad i found amanda.
罗斯你们只出去过一次
Ross, you guys went out once.
你们带着孩子去吃了一顿  小鸡奶酪
You took your kids to chuck e. cheese,
你都没亲她
and you didn't even kiss her.
我会泄露秘密
I tell people secrets.
好让别人喜欢我
It makes them like me.
菲比
Phoebe.
你生病了别唱了  回家上床休息吧
You're sick. you shouldn't play. go home.
但是我失业了
But i'm unemployed.
我只剩下音乐
My music is all i really have now.
音乐还有自己做鞋子很美吧
Well, music and making my own shoes. pretty, huh?
好我去
All right, i'm gonna do it.
我去接受枪毙
I'm gonna go get shot down.
有什么建议
Any advice?
展现你的本色
Just be yourself...
但是不要太过
...but not too much.
祝我好运
Wish me luck.
加油
Good luck!
请用祈祷的
Wish it!
你好  我坐在那里
I was just sitting over there and....
我是钱德勒  我有说吗
My name's chandler. did i say that?
没有  你好  我是凯西
No, you didn't. hi, i'm kathy.
-K开头的还是C开头的凯西  -K开头的
-kathy with a k or a c? -with a k.
你还真会搭讪
Wow, you are really good at this!
别这么说我很尴尬
Hey, come on, give me a break, I'm out on a limb here.
你说得对我道歉
I'm sorry, you're right, I apologize,
但是我跟别人有约
But i should tell you, i'm waiting for a date.
他来了
And there he is now!
你们已经认识了
I see you guys already met.
是啊我正在示范
Yes-yes, I was just trying to figure out a way to uh,
如何把我那很大的脚
demonstrate how I could get my exceptionally large feet
塞进我那更大的嘴里
into my even bigger mouth.
我就说吧
Didn't i tell you?
他最爱现了
Always showing off.
首先我要说我感冒了
Before i start, i want to say that i have a cold.
要是我唱到一半打喷嚏  那不是故意的
So if i sneeze during a song, it's not on purpose.
除了胡椒人的最后一句
Oh, except the last verse of Pepper People.
臭臭猫臭臭猫
Smelly cat, smelly cat.
他们喂你吃什么
What are they feeding you?
这声音不赖喔
This chick sounds good.
臭臭猫臭臭
Smelly cat
甘瑟乖孩子拿杯威士忌来
Gunther, be a good little boy and bring me a whiskey.
想不到半夜2点半  还要抢遥控器
2:30a.m., i didn't expect to have to fight over the remote.
对不起  我想看厄尼柯瓦克斯的节目
Sorry, there's this ernie kovacs thing i wanted to watch.
我也是要看那个
That's why i got up too.
不会吧我爱死他了
You're kidding? I love him!
下午很抱歉
I'm sorry about this afternoon. if I had
要是知道你们我也不会
known that you two, I met in acting class.
没什么
Oh, please.
乔伊说你们是在表演课认识的
Joey tells me you two met in acting class.
对我们两个一组
They teamed us up as partners.
乔伊选了三场戏
joey picked three scenes for us to do
三场都是亲热戏
All of them had us making out.
这还真不错
That's a good thing actually, because ah,
以前他总是一个人排练亲热戏
he used to have me rehearse with him.
-开始了吗  -神奇笤帚太棒了
-ls it on? -no, but this wonder broom is amazing!
上帝啊
Oh my God!
开始了
Oh! It's on! It's on!
小不点过来
There we go little fella.
那鸭子呢
What about the duck?
鸭子会游泳
The duck can swim.
烂泥巴鞋
My sticky shoes
沾满烂泥巴的鞋
My sticky, sticky shoes
你为什么黏着我不放
Why you stick on me?
宝贝
Baby
谢谢你的灯光亲爱的
Thanks for the lights, honey.
太精彩了
Way to go!
你的声音好有磁性
Your cold makes you sound great.
好好玩我真是太性感了
It's fun. god, i love how sexy i am!
凯西该走了  我们要去买仓鼠
Kath, we should get going. we're going to buy hamsters.
我喜欢仓鼠
I love them.
不是那样的  我在替一个医疗研究员工作
No, it's not like that. i work for a medical researcher.
-去玩吧  -好
-well, have fun. -okay.
医学界总算也在救助
It's nice that the medical community...
生病的仓鼠了
...is trying to help sick hamsters.
我喜欢凯西  对啊
You know what? i like kathy.
我也是她好酷好漂亮
Me too! she's so cool and pretty.
是啊
She is.
她既聪明又风趣
She's smart and funny.
我们昨晚聊了一整夜
We were up all last night talking.
她聊到一些
she said the funndler loves kathy
怎样
What?
你爱她
You love her.
我没有
No, i don't.
你有钱德勒爱凯西
Yes, you do. chandler loves kathy.
-菲比饶了他吧  -谢了罗斯
-Come on, Pheebs just lay off him. -Thank you, Ross.
他现在有点敏感  因为他恋爱了
Yeah, he's a little sensitive right now, `cause he's so in love.
好啦
All right.
凯西我爱你
Kathy, i love you!
我得写一些悲情的歌
I need to write some depressing stuff
来配合我的新哭腔
to go with my ne
但是我没有悲惨的遭遇
But nothing that sad has ever really happened to me.
你妈自杀的事呢
How about your mom dying?
或是你14岁时流落街头
Or having to live on the streets when you were 14?
我可以写头发翘起来那次
I could write about the time my hair did that wh
我晚上要去亚曼达家
I'm going over to amanda's tonight.
瑞秋不在
Rachel's not here.
你跟她进展如何
How's it going with her?
很棒搞不好今晚就有机会
Great, actually. i'm thinking tonight may be the night.
两个孩子会一起玩  等他们睡了
The kids are gonna play together, and then when th
我们自己来玩
do a little playing ourselves.
亚曼达和我再开一瓶酒
I'm thinking amanda and i break open a bottle of wine
这是约什
Hi, guys! this is josh.
约什  她们是我的朋友
Josh, these are my friends.
那是罗斯
And that's ross.
老兄
Dudes.
你在大学校队打球
You played in college?
现在还是明年我想进大学代表队
I still do. next year, i hope to make varsity.
罗斯你高中不是踢过足球吗
Didn't you play soccer in high school?
不对  你只是用游戏机帮他们排赛程表
No, wait. you just organized their game schedules on w. isn't he great?
不早了我还有球赛  先闪了
It's getting late. i gotta get to the game, so i'
我会想你的
I'll miss you.
爽
Dope!
很可爱嘛
Wow! cute one.
-非常可爱  -我知道他很棒吧
-very cute. -i know. isn't he great?
总算来了一段有趣的恋情
So nice to finally be in a fun relationship, you know?
他一点也不无聊
There's nothing boring about him.
我敢赌他一定没进过博物馆
I bet he's never set foot in a museum.
也许他快要有机会了
Maybe he'll get to go soon.
像班级旅行什么的
Like on a class trip or something.
你们知道他还有哪里好
You know what else is great about him?
该怎么形容
What is the word for an adult...
房间里没有恐龙玩具的男人
...who doesn't have dinosaur toys in their bedroom?
什么意思
What was that?
莫妮卡知道
Monica knows.
那是罗斯发明来唬爸妈的
It's this dumb thing that ross made up to try to fo get ready...
其实就是竖中指的意思
It's a way of giving the finger without actually hyou made that up.
你发明这个手势让我哭了
I remember I cried the night you made it up,
我第一次明白
Cause it was the first time that I realized
我比我哥酷
was cooler than get ready...
我要去准备
I'm going to go get ready...
赴今晚的约了
...for my date tonight...
先闪了
...so i'll just "head."
我也该走了1小时后要上台
I should go too. i'm playing in one hour.
你们应该来听  来听
You guys should come hear me.
来吧
Hear me.
烂泥巴鞋
My sticky shoes
我的性感破锣嗓没了
I lost my sexy phlegm!
小本
Hi, ben.
-你好美  -谢谢
-Wow! You-you look great! -Thanks!
汤米
Hey Tommy.
我好高兴你今晚能来
I am so glad that you could come over tonight.
不这是我的荣幸
Oh no-no-no, it's my pleasure.
我的手机号码在餐台上
Okay, well, my cell phone number is right here on the counter,
冰箱里的东西自己拿
please help yourself to anything in the fridge.
真的很谢谢你
I appreciate this soo much,
我想约这个男的好久了
I've been trying to go out with this guy for like a month. ...this guy for a month.
有一点想要提醒你
Oh, I don't mean to be a square,
能不能请你等孩子睡了再喝酒
but I'd really appreciate it if you wait and drink your wine after the kids are asleep?
谢谢你希望改天我也能帮你
Oh uh, thanks for this, I hope I can do the same for you sometime.
谁想打长途电话
Who wants to make some long distance calls?
凯西  凯西
Kathy! kathy! hi!
Kathy! kathy!
凯西
Kathy!
去接去接
Fetch! fetch it!
凯西  凯西
Kathy! kathy!
凯西
Kathy!
钱德勒你怎么在这里
Chandler, what are you doing here?
我只是来打个招呼
I just wanted to say, "hey!"
好
Hey.
好了
Okay.
你说得太严重了吧
You're making it sound worse than it was.
她的男伴给了我10块钱
Her date tipped me $10!
菲比你干什么
Pheebs, what are you doing?
我想恢复性感所以我想感冒
Okay, I wanna be sexy again so I'm trying to catch a cold.
应该很容易感冒很常见
It should be easy, supposedly they're pretty common.
你会得肺炎
Phoebe, you'll catch pneumonia.
你们说得对  我爱上了乔伊的女朋友
Okay. You were right. I'm in love with Joey's girlfriend.
什么  真的吗
What?! Are you serious?
怎么可能你们根本不熟
Well, how-how-how is that possible? You barely know her!
我不晓得我就是
I don't know. I can't--I just
我就是无法忘掉她
I can't get her out of my head.
我很糟糕非常非常糟
I'm a very bad person. i'm a very, very bad person.
我是个烂人
I'm a horrible person.
才不是呢钱德勒我们还是爱你
"no, you're not. we still love you, chandler!"
我染上你的感冒了
Phoebe, i think i caught your cold.
是偷走才对
You mean you stole it!
打喷嚏不要捂嘴巴
Don't cover your mouth when you do that!
我们正在说你
We were just talking about you.
真的
Really?
对就是你喝醉  头泡在马桶里睡着那次
The time you got drunk and fell asleep... ...with your head in the toilet.
就是在那里
Right in there!
100   我来捉你们了
...a hundred. ready or not, here i come!
我再解释一次规则
All right, let's go over the concept one more time.
小家伙们  晚上要不要跟我们吃饭
Hey guys. You want to get some dinner with me and kathy tonight?
我已经吃饱了
You know what? i already ate.
才4点半
It's 4:30.
我星期一中饭吃得很饱
Y'know I had a big meal on Monday, y'know.
可以撑一整个礼拜
So that'll get me straight through the week.
好我知道是怎么回事
I see what's going on here.
-你知道  是的
-You-you do? -yeah.
你讨厌凯西
You don't like kathy.
被你猜对了
You got me.
我们交往至今你一直在躲她
Yeah, you've been avoiding her ever since we started going out.
我曾经努力去喜欢珍妮丝
I made an effort to like Janice,
现在该你试着去喜欢凯西
now I think it's your turn to make an effort to like Kathy
-是的  -好的  算我的
-yeah, right. -good. and hey, my treat.
-不过你不吃对吧  -对
-only because you're not eating, right? -right.
罗斯不在
Ross isn't here.
放手
Stop it!
那我们派对上见
I'll see you at the party?
啤酒免费  24小时乘以七天
Beer's fear, man! twenty-four, seven!
我一定会嫁给他
I am so gonna marry that guy.
怎么了
What?
-我觉得他偷我的钱  -为啥
-i think he's stealing from me. -why?
为什么  因为他真的偷我的钱
Why? Because he's stealing from me!
是我
Hi! It's me
还有热汤
...and soup.
我刚遇到约什他穿你的皮衣看起来好帅
Hey, I just saw Josh, he looks so yummy in your leather jacket.
来我不吃鸡所以只有汤
Here, now I don't eat chicken, so it's just noodle soup.
熬汤时又没放鸡跟水没两样
And there's no chicken in the broth either, so it's really just... noodle water.
-谢谢  -不客气
-thank you so much. -sure.
你干嘛
What are you doing?
我要你的细菌  我想再感冒
I need your germs. i want my cold back.
我怀念我的性感嗓音
I miss my sexy voice.
对不起
Sorry, phoebe.
没关系
It's okay.
汤如何
How's the soup?
那个女生的内衣都露出来了
Check it out! you can see that girl's underwear.
她很棒吧
Is she great, or what?
你觉得她如何
What do you think?
她不是我的型
She's not really my type.
不是你的型  大美女耶
Not your type? she's gorgeous.
因为她穿网袜
You know what it is? the fishnet stockings.
看到女生穿网袜我就想到
Whenever i see a girl in fishnet
我爸穿网袜的样子
stockings, it rdropped me off. ...my father in fishnet stockings.
好吧  我有点了解你为何单身了
Okay. Understanding a little more why you're single.
我有个很漂亮的朋友
Ohh! Y'know, I have a friend you would like,
我们可以一起约会
she's really pretty.And then we could double date!
不用了
No, thanks.
好  我也有几个丑朋友没有对象
Okay, I've got some ugly friends, and they're all available too.
我去叫酒
Listen, I-I'm gonna grab a beer.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
-你什么意思  -什么
-What was that? -What?
凯西在示好你却掉头就走
Kathy's being really nice and you just walked away.Ithought we had
你要我怎样
What do you want from me?
我要你喜欢她
I want you to like her.
要是太难了
If that's too damn difficult for you,
你起码可以装一下
then the least you chen do it better.
-我正在装啊  -那就再像一点
-i am pretending. -then do it better.
好不如我去
Okay, what do you saw I go over there
说我很喜欢她
and tell her how some cough drop
我可以说我一直在想她
No-no it'll be good, I can tell her much I've been thinking about her.
认识之后我就一直想着她
That I haven't stopped thinking about her since the moment I met her.
我无可救药  简直想掐死自己的爱着她
I'm so over the top, want-to-slit-my-own-throat...
每一天的每一分每一秒
...in love with her that for every minute...
我都在怨恨
...i can't believe my own damn
为何是你先认识她
bad luck that yo some cough drop
很不错
That's pretty good.
但是别那么夸张
But you might want to tone it down a little.
是亚曼达载我来的
Hey! So, uhh, Amanda just-just dropped me off.
我就喜欢她这一点
Yeah, that's one of the things I love about her,
成年人可以开车
She's old enough to drive.
你晚上不去找爸妈了
You're not going to mom and dad's tonight?
不了对不起
No, sorry.
亚曼达呢
Where's amanda?
瑞秋帮我拿咳嗽药水好吗
Could you get me some cough drops?
我在想
I'm thinking
你可以带她去你的旧房间
you could bring her... ...
然后不上床
and you guys could not making out
咳嗽药  谢谢
Cough drop, please?
至少她跟我出去
At least she's not going out with me...
不是为了看限制级电影
...to get into r-rated movies.
你怎么不娶她算了
Why don't you just marry her?
我忘了你不行  她不是同性恋
Wait, you can't! i forgot. she's not a lesbian.
-亚曼达和我  -什么都不是
- You see Amanda and I have a very special...- You have nothing!
你们根本没在约会  你是她的保姆
You're not even going out! You're her baby sitter!
你在做12岁小女生做的事
You have a 12-year-old girl's job!
真可悲啊
Ohh, that is soo sad.
你笑什么  你男朋友还不是爱喝酒又偷钱
And what are you laughing at, Miss `My-keg-sucking-boyfriend-is-stealing-from-me!'
他偷了几块钱又怎样  他有买东西给我
Hey, so he stole a couple bucks from me! At least he bought me something with it!
那是我的
That's mine!
你们两个成熟一点好吗
Would you both please start acting like adults?
把咳嗽药水拿给我
And give me my cough drops!
-好  -对不起
-fine. -sorry.
拿去
Here.
谢谢
Thank you.
至少我还赚了10块钱
At least I made ten bucks in my relationship.
去死吧
You know...?
游行的山羊在游行
Platting goats are platting,
在大街上游行
Parading down the street
游行的山羊在游行
Parading goats are parading
留下小脚印
Leaving little treats
用这种声音唱还能听吗
Does it even work without my sexy voice?
我喜欢
I like it.
-甘瑟亲我  -什么
-gunther, kiss me. -what?
副警长快想办法
Do it, deputy! do something!
我们没有要睡但是小声点好吗
We aren't exactly sleeping in here, but do you mind?
我可以睡你的沙发吗
Can i sleep on your couch?
我还在等
And i'm still waiting
我的纸黏土人
For my papier-mache man
谢谢各位
Thank you my babies.
瑞秋  怎样
Rachel? Yeah.
我不知道你有没有听说我和菲比的事
I don't know if you heard about what happened between me and Phoebe the other day_
没啊
No.
我们接吻了  不是我主动的但我也没阻止
We kissed. i didn't initiate it, but i also didn't stop it.
我一直觉得很内疚
I've been feeling guilty.
好吧
Okay.
所以
So...
我们没事吧
...are we cool?
好吧
Okay.
就知道你会理解的
I knew you would understand.